Good morning. I know that it's, like, really hip to be involved in politics these days, but I just want y'all to know that the United States is essentially the United Nations in the fact that it is a pseudo-democracy.
What's pseudo mean, Amanda? A fake democratic performance that engages all those involved to feel like they are a part of the governing system, when in actuality, they are not.
The Security Council is the Electoral College. We are simply just, like, countries, we are the citizens of the United States, participating to look like we are doing something, when in actuality, we are literally just being constantly distracted so that we are not focusing our energy on those who are controlling us. So, hope this helps.
Then, Amanda, why do you keep talking about politics? Because I'm trying to use it as a tool to create a level of awareness that will decolonize, folks.
However, I have realized that so many of you all have actually taken on the very American trait of arrogant ignorance, and thus, you will be a willing aid to your own demise.
Welcome to our store.
Thank you, big boy.
I love you.
My neighbor.
Where's that?